Guide to the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1964-1986 (bulk 1975-1984)
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1964-1986 (bulk 1975-1984)
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean records, 1964-1986 (bulk 1975-1984)
24-01-3380
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine Office of the Dean
3 cubic ft.
Subject files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence and subject files compiled by the Office of the Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine during Edward C. Melby's tenure as dean.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Edward C. Melby, Jr. was Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine from 1975-1984.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence and subject files compiled by the Office of the Dean of the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine during Edward C. Melby's tenure as dean.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Melby, Edward C.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
In original order.
CONTAINER LIST
- Faculty Salaries/Retention- Report to Dr. Mou, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Provost/Vice Provost, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Tug Hill, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Drug Testing Program - Maylin, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Foreign Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cornell Deans' Council, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- SEA Grant - Governing Board Meeting, May 15, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Congressional Hearings, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Funding for College Programs, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- State Reimbursement Policy for Diagnostic Laboratory, Mastitis Control Program, Poultry Disease Lab, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hearings, Albany, March 8, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hearings, Albany, March 8, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Albany Meetings, Feb 23-24, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Enhanced Support from NYS Legislature, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bovine Health Research Center, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bovine Health Research Center, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bovine Health Research Center, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bovine Health Research Center - Dedication, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bovine Health Research Center - Emerson/Ryan, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Equine Advisory Council, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Contagious Equine Metritis, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Equine Research Center/Program, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Equine Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Proposed Regional Laboratory, Southeastern New York State, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Nutritional Sciences Building - Equine Sports Medicine Program, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Woodchuck Project, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Chairmen's Retreats 1974-1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Hospital Staff Memos, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Lab Animal Medicine, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Research -Venture Capital - Industry, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Research -Venture Capital - Industry, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Research -Venture Capital - Industry, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Venture Capital Funding Workshop, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Veterinary Science, Inc. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Veterinary Science, Inc. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Veterinary Science, Inc. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Genentech, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Genentech, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- California Biotech, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- SDS Biotech Corp, Nov 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Master Plan, 1964 (Box 2)
- Master Plan, 1968 (Box 2)
- Master Plan, 1973-1980 (Box 2)
- Master Plan, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Master Plan, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Long Range Plan, Sept 15, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Five Year Plan for Fiscal Facilities Revitalization, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Enhanced Support, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Enhanced Support, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Enhanced Support, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Blue Ribbon Committee, Nov. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Accreditation - Volume I (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Accreditation - Volume I (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Accreditation - Volume II (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Accreditation - Volume II (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Accreditation - Volume III (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Accreditation - Volume III (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Accreditation - Volume IV (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Accreditation - Volume IV (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Accreditation - Volume V (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Accreditation - Volume V (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Accreditation - Volume VI (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Accreditation - Volume VI (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Accreditation - Volume VII (folder 1), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Accreditation - Volume VII (folder 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Accreditation Information, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Accreditation? "Clinical Data", 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Accreditation - "Course Outlines", ca. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Accreditation - Personnel Reports, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Accreditation - Personnel Reports, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Accreditation, 1972, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Statutory College Budget Request, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)